<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Internship Report</title>
    <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/index.html</link>
    <description>Student Information&#xD;Full Name: Dương Bình Minh&#xA;Phone Number: 0355578938&#xA;Email: duongbinhminh10032004@gmail.com&#xA;University: Sai Gon University&#xA;Major: Information Technology&#xA;Class: DCT1226&#xA;Internship Company: Amazon Web Services Vietnam Co., Ltd.&#xA;Internship Position: FCJ Cloud Intern&#xA;Internship Duration: From 12/08/2025 to 12/11/2025&#xA;Internship Company: Amazon Web Services Vietnam Co., Ltd.&#xA;Internship Position: FCJ Cloud Intern&#xA;Internship Duration: From 29/09/2025 to 22/11/2025</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Worklog</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/index.html</guid>
      <description>Week 1: Orientation, team formation, and building a foundational understanding of AWS services and tools required for the program&#xA;Week 2: Explore and practice core VPC and EC2 concepts through hands-on configuration, foundational networking setup, and initial project planning activities.&#xA;Week 3: Study and apply Route 53 and CloudFormation concepts while progressing solution architecture design and setting up foundational backend, frontend, and database components.&#xA;Week 4: Develop backend authentication and frontend foundations while exploring S3 and API Gateway services, defining required APIs, translating technical blogs, and establishing core project architecture and UI structure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proposal</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/2-proposal/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/2-proposal/index.html</guid>
      <description>Cost-Optimized SaaS Task Management Platform&#xD;Single-Region High Availability with ECS Fargate&#xD;1. Executive Summary&#xD;The SaaS Task Management Platform is designed to deliver a Todoist-like collaborative experience with High Availability (HA) and Cost Efficiency, specifically optimized for AWS Free Tier constraints.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Translated Blogs</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/3-translated_blogs/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/3-translated_blogs/index.html</guid>
      <description>Blog 1: Những hiểu biết sâu sắc và bài học kinh nghiệm từ Amazon Q trong tích hợp trình thu thập thông tin web Connect&#xA;Blog 2: Xây dựng hệ thống đa tenant resilient với hàng đợi công bằng Amazon SQS&#xA;Blog 3: Amazon Braket ra mắt bộ xử lý lượng tử siêu dẫn 54-qubit IQM Emerald</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Events Participated</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/4-events_participated/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/4-events_participated/index.html</guid>
      <description>During my internship, I participated in two events. Each one was a memorable experience that provided new, interesting, and useful knowledge, along with gifts and wonderful moments.&#xA;Event 1&#xD;Event Name: Kick-off AWS FCJ Workforce - FPTU OJT FALL 2025&#xA;Date &amp; Time: 8:30 AM Saturday, September 6, 2025&#xA;Location: 26th Floor, Bitexco Tower, 02 Hai Trieu Street, Saigon Ward, Ho Chi Minh City</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workshop</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/5-workshop/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/5-workshop/index.html</guid>
      <description>Cost-Optimized SaaS Task Management Platform&#xD;Overview&#xD;SGU TodoList is a robust and resilient task management application built using a Microservices architecture designed for high scalability and decoupling. The primary goal of this workshop is to guide you through deploying and managing a complex application stack on the AWS Cloud platform, with a strong focus on cost optimization and serverless operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self Assesment</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/6-self-assesment/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/6-self-assesment/index.html</guid>
      <description>During my internship at AMAZON WEB SERVICES VIETNAM COMPANY LIMITED from 08/09/2025 to 09/12/2025, I had the opportunity to learn, practice, and apply the knowledge acquired in school to a real-world working environment.&#xA;I participated in developing a Multi-region SaaS Task Management Web Application, through which I enhanced my skills in Backend Development, AWS Services, and Cloud Architecture. In the backend domain, I strengthened my ability to:&#xA;Develop RESTful APIs Work with Microservices Architecture Effectively utilize various AWS services I also gained practical experience in designing AWS architectures that are scalable, secure, and cost-optimized for real-world projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharing and Feedback</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/7-sharing_and_feedback/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/7-sharing_and_feedback/index.html</guid>
      <description>Overall Evaluation&#xD;1. Working Environment&#xA;The working environment is incredibly friendly, open, and supportive. FCAJ members are always willing to help each other whenever an issue arises, and everyone is very open to discussing not only work-related topics but also studies, hobbies, and personal interests. The workspace itself is comfortable and well-organized, creating a productive atmosphere that makes it easier to stay focused and engaged.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>