<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Week 6 Worklog :: Internship Report</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.6-week_6/index.html</link>
    <description>Week 6 Objectives&#xD;Continue frontend and backend development Explore Elasticache for Redis and Amazon RDS services Tasks to be carried out this week&#xD;Day Task Start Date Completion Date Reference Material 1 - Team meeting to discuss about the development process 13/10/2025 13/10/2025 - Code backend Authentication Service, User Service - Code frontend: Build complex forms for Creating/Editing data. Apply form validation. 2 - Learn about Elasticache for Redis 14/10/2025 14/10/2025 Amazon AWS ElastiCache Deployment, AWS Elasticache Redis Creation and redis-cli Configuration step by step process - Code backend Authentication Service, User Service - Code frontend: Build complex forms for Creating/Editing data. Apply form validation. - Integrate message sending via Kafka into the Taskflow Service so it can notify the Notification Service to send alerts to users. 3 - Update worklog 15/10/2025 15/10/2025 - Code backend Authentication Service, User Service - Code frontend: Build complex forms for Creating/Editing data. Apply form validation. Develop Detail Page and integrate Get By ID API. Build advanced Search/Filter functionality. - Learn and integrate WebSocket into the Notification Service to deliver real-time notifications to users. 4 - Learn and practice Amazon RDS 16/10/2025 16/10/2025 Module 06-02 - Amazon RDS &amp; Amazon Aurora, Module 06-Lab05-2.3 - Create RDS Security group, Module 06-Lab05-4 - Create RDS database instance - Code backend Authentication Service, User Service - Code frontend: Develop Detail Page and integrate Get By ID API. Build advanced Search/Filter functionality. 5 - Code backend Authentication Service, User Service 17/10/2025 17/10/2025 - Code frontend: Develop Detail Page and integrate Get By ID API. Build advanced Search/Filter functionality. - Develop the Upcoming Task UI for the project and integrate the API calls from the Taskflow Service. - Update worklog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.6-week_6/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  </channel>
</rss>