<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Week 5 Worklog :: Internship Report</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.5-week_5/index.html</link>
    <description>Week 5 Objectives&#xD;Continue frontend and backend development Learn EC2 Auto Scaling Group Practice AWS CloudShell setups Translate blogs. Tasks to be carried out this week&#xD;Day Task Start Date Completion Date Reference Material 1 - Team meeting to discuss about the development process 06/10/2025 06/10/2025 - Translate blogs Translated Blog 6, Translated Blog 7 - Code backend Authentication Service, User Service - Install state management library (Redux), define the initial State Model, integrate API services for Login/Register pages. 2 - Learn and practice EC2 Auto Scaling Group 07/10/2025 07/10/2025 Module-03-02 - EC2 Autoscaling - EFS/FSx - Lightsail - MGN, AWS EC2 Auto Scaling : Step By Step Tutorial - Code backend Authentication Service, User Service, Taskflow Service - Code frontend: Build UI for displaying main data lists (table, grid). Integrate Get List API and Pagination. - Translate blog Translated Blog 8, Translated Blog 9 3 - Code backend Authentication Service, User Service 08/10/2025 08/10/2025 - Learn and pratice Kafka for messaging - Code frontend: Build UI for displaying main data lists (table, grid). Integrate Get List API and Pagination. - Update worklog 4 - Code backend Authentication Service, User Service 09/10/2025 09/10/2025 - Code frontend: Build UI for displaying main data lists (table, grid). Integrate Get List API and Pagination. - Learn about Caching to apply cache for database - Translate blog Translated Blog 10, Translated Blog 11 5 - Learn and practice using CloudShell 10/10/2025 10/10/2025 AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Certification Course (CLF-C02) - Translate blog Translated Blog 12</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.5-week_5/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  </channel>
</rss>