<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Worklog :: Internship Report</title>
    <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/index.html</link>
    <description>Week 1: Orientation, team formation, and building a foundational understanding of AWS services and tools required for the program&#xA;Week 2: Explore and practice core VPC and EC2 concepts through hands-on configuration, foundational networking setup, and initial project planning activities.&#xA;Week 3: Study and apply Route 53 and CloudFormation concepts while progressing solution architecture design and setting up foundational backend, frontend, and database components.&#xA;Week 4: Develop backend authentication and frontend foundations while exploring S3 and API Gateway services, defining required APIs, translating technical blogs, and establishing core project architecture and UI structure.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 1 Worklog</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.1-week_1/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.1-week_1/index.html</guid>
      <description>Week 1 Objectives&#xD;Learn the regulations Connect with other FCJ members Form team and decide team project Understand and practice basic AWS services Tasks to be carried out this week&#xD;Day Task Start Date Completion Date Reference Material 1 - Get acquainted with FCJ members 08/09/2025 08/09/2025 - Read and take note of internship unit rules and regulations Rules and regulations - Learn and practice making a static website with Hugo Hugo quickstart, Learn Hugo Theme - Create AWS account. Practice creating Users group, Users (IAM user) Create AWS account; Create user, group user 2 - Learn and practice creating Budget (Template &amp; Custom: Cost, Usage, Saving plans, Reservation) 09/09/2025 09/09/2025 Create budget - Update worklog Sample worklog 3 - Learn about support packages, types of support request, how to create a support 10/09/2025 10/09/2025 Support packages 4 - Update worklog (UI) 11/09/2025 11/09/2025 5 - Learn theory about VPC (Subnet, Route Table, Internet Gateway, NAT Gateway) 12/09/2025 12/09/2025 AWS Virtual Private Cloud - Update worklog</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 2 Worklog</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.2-week_2/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.2-week_2/index.html</guid>
      <description>Week 2 Objectives&#xD;Study Module 1 practicing VPC and EC2 Learn and practice configure VPC, EC2 and their related features Assign tasks for team project Update worklog structure Tasks to be carried out this week&#xD;Day Task Start Date Completion Date Reference Material 1 - Learn about VPC and its feature 15/09/2025 15/09/2025 VPC, Youtube Lesson 2 - Practice creating VPC, Subnets, Internet Gateway 16/09/2025 16/09/2025 Create VPC, Create Subnets, Create Internet Gateway - Update worklog 3 - Practice creating Route table, Security groups 17/09/2025 17/09/2025 Create Route Table, Create Security Groups - Decide project scopes, assgign tasks 4 - Learn about Deploying Amazon EC2 Instances 18/09/2025 18/09/2025 Deploying Amazon EC2 Instances, Youtube Tutorial - Practice creating EC2 server, Checking connection, creating NAT Gateway Create EC2 instance, Check connection, Create NAT Gateway 5 - Practice using Reachability Analyzer 19/09/2025 19/09/2025 Create Reachability Analyzer - Team meeting to decide proposal project - Update worklog</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 3 Worklog</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.3-week_3/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.3-week_3/index.html</guid>
      <description>Week 3 Objectives&#xD;Study Module 2 in the First Cloud Journey Bootcamp – 2025 playlist Learn and get familiar with Route 53, CloudFormation and their related features Design the database and set up Backend &amp; Frontend Update worklog structure Tasks to be carried out this week&#xD;Day Task Start Date Completion Date Reference Material 1 - Learn about Route 53 and its feature 22/09/2025 22/09/2025 Route 53 2 - Practice creating Key pair, CloudFormation Template, Configure Security Group 23/09/2025 23/09/2025 Create Key pair, Initialize CloudFormation Template 3 - Practice creating Key pair, CloudFormation Template, Configure Security Group 24/09/2025 24/09/2025 Create Key pair, Initialize CloudFormation Template, Configure Security Group - Team meeting and discuss about Database design, Backend, Frontend 4 - Practice connecting to Remote Desktop Gateway (RDGW) by Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) 25/09/2025 25/09/2025 Connecting to RDGW, Youtube tutorial - Design solution architecture - Team meeting to discuss about workshop project 5 - Practice deploy Microsoft Active Directory 26/09/2025 26/09/2025 Deploy Microsoft Active Directory - Practice deploy Microsoft Active Directory Deploy Microsoft Active Directory - Pratice configure DNS Configure DNS - Update worklog</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 4 Worklog</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.4-week_4/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.4-week_4/index.html</guid>
      <description>Week 4 Objectives&#xD;Begin coding the backend authentication service and frontend Discuss and list the APIs required for the taskflow service. Learn and practice S3 Explore API Gateway Translate technical blogs. Tasks to be carried out this week&#xD;Day Task Start Date Completion Date Reference Material 1 - Team meeting to discuss about the architecture, backend and front end configuration 29/09/2025 29/09/2025 - Research and make a list of APIs needed for the TaskFlow Service. 2 - Learn and practice S3 service 30/09/2025 30/09/2025 S3 lesson - Code backend Authentication Service 3 - Code backend Authentication Service 01/10/2025 01/10/2025 - Initialize the project (React, environment configuration, basic routing setup, folder structure, Git integration). 4 - Learn and practice API Gateway service 02/10/2025 02/10/2025 AWS API Gateway Introduction, Tạo API sử dụng Amazon API Gateway AWS Serverless Development Journey - Code backend Authentication Service - Set up UI/CSS libraries (e.g., Tailwind, Material UI), define global CSS variables, build basic Components (Button, Input, Card). 5 - Code backend Authentication Service 03/10/2025 03/10/2025 - Set up UI/CSS libraries (e.g., Tailwind, Material UI), define global CSS variables, build basic Components (Button, Input, Card). - Code frontend: Build Header, Footer, Sidebar, and the Landing Page. Ensure basic responsive design.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 5 Worklog</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.5-week_5/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.5-week_5/index.html</guid>
      <description>Week 5 Objectives&#xD;Continue frontend and backend development Learn EC2 Auto Scaling Group Practice AWS CloudShell setups Translate blogs. Tasks to be carried out this week&#xD;Day Task Start Date Completion Date Reference Material 1 - Team meeting to discuss about the development process 06/10/2025 06/10/2025 - Code backend Authentication Service, User Service - Install state management library (Redux), define the initial State Model, integrate API services for Login/Register pages. 2 - Learn and practice EC2 Auto Scaling Group 07/10/2025 07/10/2025 Module-03-02 - EC2 Autoscaling - EFS/FSx - Lightsail - MGN, AWS EC2 Auto Scaling : Step By Step Tutorial - Code backend Authentication Service, User Service, Taskflow Service - Code frontend: Build UI for displaying main data lists (table, grid). Integrate Get List API and Pagination. 3 - Code backend Authentication Service, User Service 08/10/2025 08/10/2025 - Learn and pratice Kafka for messaging - Code frontend: Build UI for displaying main data lists (table, grid). Integrate Get List API and Pagination. - Update worklog 4 - Code backend Authentication Service, User Service 09/10/2025 09/10/2025 - Code frontend: Build UI for displaying main data lists (table, grid). Integrate Get List API and Pagination. - Learn about Caching to apply cache for database 5 - Learn and practice using CloudShell 10/10/2025 10/10/2025 AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Certification Course (CLF-C02)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 6 Worklog</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.6-week_6/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.6-week_6/index.html</guid>
      <description>Week 6 Objectives&#xD;Continue frontend and backend development Explore Elasticache for Redis and Amazon RDS services Tasks to be carried out this week&#xD;Day Task Start Date Completion Date Reference Material 1 - Team meeting to discuss about the development process 13/10/2025 13/10/2025 - Code backend Authentication Service, User Service - Code frontend: Build complex forms for Creating/Editing data. Apply form validation. 2 - Learn about Elasticache for Redis 14/10/2025 14/10/2025 Amazon AWS ElastiCache Deployment, AWS Elasticache Redis Creation and redis-cli Configuration step by step process - Code backend Authentication Service, User Service - Code frontend: Build complex forms for Creating/Editing data. Apply form validation. - Integrate message sending via Kafka into the Taskflow Service so it can notify the Notification Service to send alerts to users. 3 - Update worklog 15/10/2025 15/10/2025 - Code backend Authentication Service, User Service - Code frontend: Build complex forms for Creating/Editing data. Apply form validation. Develop Detail Page and integrate Get By ID API. Build advanced Search/Filter functionality. - Learn and integrate WebSocket into the Notification Service to deliver real-time notifications to users. 4 - Learn and practice Amazon RDS 16/10/2025 16/10/2025 Module 06-02 - Amazon RDS &amp; Amazon Aurora, Module 06-Lab05-2.3 - Create RDS Security group, Module 06-Lab05-4 - Create RDS database instance - Code backend Authentication Service, User Service - Code frontend: Develop Detail Page and integrate Get By ID API. Build advanced Search/Filter functionality. 5 - Code backend Authentication Service, User Service 17/10/2025 17/10/2025 - Code frontend: Develop Detail Page and integrate Get By ID API. Build advanced Search/Filter functionality. - Develop the Upcoming Task UI for the project and integrate the API calls from the Taskflow Service. - Update worklog</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 7 Worklog</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.7-week_7/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.7-week_7/index.html</guid>
      <description>Week 7 Objectives&#xD;Code Backend User Service and Notification Service Code Frontend Explore the Application Load Balancer service Learn how to deploy the system on cloud resources Test deploying the Frontend on S3 Tasks to be carried out this week&#xD;Day Task Start Date Completion Date Reference Material 1 - Team meeting to discuss about the development process 20/10/2025 20/10/2025 - Code backend User Service, Notification Service - Code frontend: Develop Detail Page and integrate Get By ID API. Build advanced Search/Filter functionality. 2 - Learn about Application Load Balancer 21/10/2025 21/10/2025 AWS ALB (Application Load Balancer) - Step By Step Tutorial, Create an Application Load Balancer (ALB) in AWS - AWS Elastic Load Balancing Tutorial for Beginners - Code backend User Service, Notification Service - Code frontend: Develop Detail Page and integrate Get By ID API. Build advanced Search/Filter functionality. 3 - Learn how to deploy the system on cloud resources 22/10/2025 22/10/2025 - Code backend User Service, Notification Service - Code frontend: Develop Detail Page and integrate Get By ID API. Build advanced Search/Filter functionality. 4 - Code backend User Service, Notification Service 23/10/2025 23/10/2025 - Code frontend: Develop Detail Page and integrate Get By ID API. Build advanced Search/Filter functionality. Build modals, popups, drag-and-drop features. Complete 80% of the main business flow. 5 - Code backend User Service, Notification Service 24/10/2025 24/10/2025 - Code frontend: Build modals, popups, drag-and-drop features. Complete 80% of the main business flow. - Test deploying the Frontend on S3</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 8 Worklog</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.8-week_8/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.8-week_8/index.html</guid>
      <description>Week 8 Objectives&#xD;Code Backend User Service and Notification Service Code Frontend Explore the Application Load Balancer service Learn how to deploy the system on cloud resources Test deploying the Frontend on S3 Tasks to be carried out this week&#xD;Day Task Start Date Completion Date Reference Material 1 - Team meeting to discuss about the development process 27/10/2025 27/10/2025 - Build the Notification interface for the project, integrate the APIs, and establish a WebSocket connection to the backend. - Check the services code 2 - Code front end: Write Unit Tests for key components and functions. Perform Integration Tests for main business flows. 28/10/2025 28/10/2025 - Code backend User Service, Notification Service - Learn and practice ALB 3 - Code front end: Write Unit Tests for key components and functions. Perform Integration Tests for main business flows. 29/10/2025 29/10/2025 - Code backend User Service, Notification Service - Experiment deploy static resource on S3 4 - Code front end: Optimize loading performance (Code Splitting, Lazy Loading). 30/10/2025 30/10/2025 - Code backend User Service, Notification Service 5 - Code front end: Improve Accessibility (A11Y) and error handling (Error Boundaries). 31/10/2025 31/10/2025</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 9 Worklog</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.9-week_9/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.9-week_9/index.html</guid>
      <description>Week 9 Objectives&#xD;Review and check backend service code Develop and integrate frontend features for Notification &amp; Auth Adjust and refine system architecture through team discussions Implement and update WebSocket for real-time notifications Integrate Google OAuth2 login for Authentication Service Fix bugs related to WebSocket reconnection and authentication state Tasks to be carried out this week&#xD;Day Task Start Date Completion Date Reference Material 1 - Team meeting to discuss about the development process 03/11/2025 03/11/2025 - Build the Notification interface for the project, integrate the APIs, and establish a WebSocket connection to the backend. - Check the services code 2 - Update WebSocket for Notification Service 04/11/2025 04/11/2025 - Refactor NotificationService flow to support real-time push notifications - Code front end: Review services UI for flaws 3 - Implement OAuth2 Login Google for Auth Service 05/11/2025 05/11/2025 - Test login flow and integrate Google OAuth callback - Update worklog 4 - Continue integrating Notification &amp; Auth features on frontend 06/11/2025 06/11/2025 - Fix bugs related to WebSocket reconnection &amp; auth state 5 - Testing for the week’s features 07/11/2025 07/11/2025 - Prepare weekly report &amp; deployment checklist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 10 Worklog</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.10-week_10/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.10-week_10/index.html</guid>
      <description>Week 10 Objectives&#xD;Conduct internal UAT for frontend, collect feedback, fix UI issues, and refine user interface throughout the week Fix backend bugs mainly in Task Service, with additional fixes in User Service Participate in team meetings to discuss development workflow, architecture adjustments, and backend issues Update worklogs and maintain progress tracking Tasks to be carried out this week&#xD;Day Task Start Date Completion Date Reference Material 1 - Team meeting to discuss about the development process 10/11/2025 10/11/2025 - Update worklog 2 - Code front end: Conduct internal UAT (User Acceptance Testing). Collect feedback and fix detected issues. Refine UI based on feedback. 11/11/2025 11/11/2025 - Code back end: Fix bugs in Task Service 3 - Code front end: Conduct internal UAT (User Acceptance Testing). Collect feedback and fix detected issues. Refine UI based on feedback. 12/11/2025 12/11/2025 - Code back end: Fix bugs in Task Service 4 - Teem meeting to discuss about the architecture, backend bugs 13/11/2025 13/11/2025 - Code front end: Conduct internal UAT (User Acceptance Testing). Collect feedback and fix detected issues. Refine UI based on feedback. - Code back end: Fix bugs in Task Service, User Service 5 - Update worklog 14/11/2025 14/11/2025 - Code front end: Conduct internal UAT (User Acceptance Testing). Collect feedback and fix detected issues. Refine UI based on feedback.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 11 Worklog</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.11-week_11/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.11-week_11/index.html</guid>
      <description>Week 11 Objectives&#xD;Find bugs and deploy Complete the solution architecture Tasks to be carried out this week&#xD;Day Task Start Date Completion Date Reference Material 1 - Team meeting to discuss about the development process 17/11/2025 17/11/2025 - Adjust the solution architecture - Code back end: Fix bugs in User Service 2 - Code back end: Fix bugs in User Service 3 - Adjust solution architecture 19/11/2025 19/11/2025 - Team meeting to review existing flaws in Frontend and Backend 4 - Adjust solution architecture 20/11/2025 20/11/2025 5 - Team meeting 21/11/2025 21/11/2025 - Experimental deploy VPC, Subnets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 12 Worklog</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.12-week_12/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.12-week_12/index.html</guid>
      <description>Week 12 Objectives&#xD;Summarize and resolve remaining issues in the system Conduct experimental deployment of S3 in a Single Region Practice and get familiar with Amazon RDS MySQL and ElastiCache for Redis Configure Google OAuth for the Authentication Service Adjust the solution architecture to be suitable for a Single Region (considering cost limitations for Free accounts) Successfully deploy frontend resources to S3 Complete the worklog and update the workshop Tasks to be carried out this week&#xD;Day Task Start Date Completion Date Reference Material 1 - Team meeting to to review issues needed to be solve 24/11/2025 24/11/2025 - Experimental S3 single region deployment 2 - Complete part 4. Events participated of Workshop 25/11/2025 25/11/2025 - Experimental S3 single region deployment 3 - Experimental VPC deployment 26/11/2025 26/11/2025 - Practice using RDS MySQL, ElastiCacheForRedis 4 - Config Google OAuth 27/11/2025 27/11/2025 - Practice using RDS MySQL, ElastiCacheForRedis 5 - Adjust solution architecture to single-region (as for Free account and cost limitations) 28/11/2025 28/11/2025 - Deploy frontend resources to S3 successfully - Update worklog, workshop</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 13 Worklog</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.13-week_13/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.13-week_13/index.html</guid>
      <description>Week 13 Objectives&#xD;Review and resolve remaining setup issues from previous deployments Set up VPC, Subnets, Internet Gateway, and Security Groups Configure Application Load Balancer (ALB) Deploy backend and frontend images to ECR and ECS Fargate Set up Amazon RDS MySQL Configure Google OAuth redirect for Authentication Service Organize and update worklog categories based on team members Tasks to be carried out this week&#xD;Day Task Start Date Completion Date Reference Material 1 - Team meeting to to review issues needed to be solve 01/11/2025 01/11/2025 - Setup VPC, Subnets, Internet Gateway, Security groups - Update worklog: create worklog categories base on team members 2 - Setup VPC, Subnets, Internet Gateway 02/11/2025 02/11/2025 - Setup ALB, Security groups, RDS MySQL 3 - Setup VPC, Subnets, Internet Gateway, Security groups 03/11/2025 03/11/2025 - Deploy images to ECR, ECS Fargate - Setup ALB, Security groups, RDS MySQL 4 - Deploy images to ECR, ECS Fargate, ALB, RDS 04/11/2025 04/11/2025 - Setup ALB, Security groups, RDS MySQL 5 - Deploy images to ECR, ECS Fargate, ALB, RDS 05/11/2025 05/11/2025 - Setup ALB, Security groups, RDS MySQL - Config Google OAuth Redirect</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 14 Worklog</title>
      <link>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.14-week_14/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://duongbinhminh1003.github.io/dbm1003/en/1-worklog/1.14-week_14/index.html</guid>
      <description>Week 14 Objectives&#xD;Complete deployment Complete workshop Run test Tasks to be carried out this week&#xD;Day Task Start Date Completion Date Reference Material 1 - Complete deploying ECS Fargate, run test 08/11/2025 08/11/2025 - Complete worklog &amp; Workshop 2 09/11/2025 09/11/2025 3 10/11/2025 10/11/2025 4 11/11/2025 11/11/2025 5 12/11/2025 12/11/2025</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>